Guide to the Sunset Magazine Records M2065
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Photograph files
  - Clippings, South and North, 1962-09 (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - September 1962 magazine (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - 9-62-001 to 9-62-092, 1962-09 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - 9-62-093 to 9-62-166, 1962-09 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - 9-62-167 to 9-62-258, 1962-09 (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1962-10 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - October 1962 magazine (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - 10-62-001 to 10-62-067, 1962-10 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - 10-62-068 to 10-62-068, 1962-10 (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - 10-62-164 to 10-62-224, 1962-10 (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - 10-62-225 to 10-62-291, 1962-10 (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - 10-62-293 to 10-62-356, 1962-10 (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1962-11 (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - November 1962 magazine (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - 11-62-000 to 11-62-062, 1962-11 (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - 11-62-063 to 11-62-126, 1962-11 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - 11-62-128 to 11-62-192, 1962-11 (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - 11-62-194 to 11-62-243, 1962-11 (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - 11-62-244 to 11-62-348, 1962-11 (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1962-12 (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - December 1962 magazine (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - 12-62-000 to 12-62-066, 1962-12 (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - 12-62-068 to 12-62-143, 1962-12 (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - 12-62-151 to 12-62-208, 1962-12 (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1963-01 (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - January 1963 Central magazine (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - 1-63-000 to 1-63-065, 1963-01 (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - 1-63-066 to 1-63-139, 1963-01 (Box 128, Folder 6)
  - 1-63-141 to 1-63-227, 1963-01 (Box 128, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1963-02 (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - February 1963 magazine (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - 2-63-000 to 2-63-078, 1963-02 (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - 2-63-079 to 2-63-196, 1963-02 (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - 2-63-198 to 2-63-275, 1963-02 (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1963-03 (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - March 1963 magazine (Box 129, Folder 7)
  - 3-63-000 to 3-63-062, 1963-03 (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - 3-63-063 to 3-63-124, 1963-03 (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - 3-63-128 to 3-63-176, 1963-03 (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - 3-63-177 to 3-63-261, 1963-03 (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - 3-63-263 to 3-36-313, 1963-03 (Box 130, Folder 4)
  - 3-63-317 to 3-63-395, 1963-03 (Box 130, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1963-04 (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - April 1963 Central magazine (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - 4-63-001 to 4-63-069, 1963-04 (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - 4-63-070 to 4-63-145, 1963-04 (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - 4-63-149 to 4-63-246, 1963-04 (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - 4-63-247 to 4-63-327, 1963-04 (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - 4-63-328 to 4-63-419, 1963-04 (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1963-05 (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - May 1963 Central magazine (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - 5-63-000 to 5-63-074, 1963-05 (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - 5-63-076 to 5-63-143, 1963-05 (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - 5-63-144 to 5-63-186, 1963-05 (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - 5-63-187 to 5-63-272, 1963-05 (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - 5-63-273 to 5-63-367, 1963-05 (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1963-06 (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - June 1963 Central magazine (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - 6-63-010 to 6-63-093, 1963-06 (Box 133, Folder 5)
  - 6-63-094 to 6-63-151, 1963-06 (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - 6-63-156 to 6-63-227, 1963-06 (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - 6-63-228 to 6-63-327, 1963-06 (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1963-07 (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - July 1963 magazine, 1963-07 (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - 7-63-000 to 7-63-077, 1963-07 (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - 7-63-078 to 7-63-163, 1963-07 (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - 7-63-165 to 7-63-220, 1963-07 (Box 134, Folder 7)
  - 7-63-221 to 7-63-306, 1963-07 (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1963-08 (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - August 1963 Central magazine (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - 8-63-000 to 8-63-061, 1963-08 (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - 8-63-062 to 8-63-120, 1963-08 (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - 8-63-124 to 8-63-235, 1963-08 (Box 135, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1963-09 (Box 135, Folder 7)
  - September 1963 Central magazine (Box 135, Folder 8)
  - 9-63-000 to 9-63-075, 1963-09 (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - 9-63-077 to 9-63-129, 1963-09 (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - 9-63-136 to 9-63-204, 1963-09 (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - 9-63-205 to 9-63-287, 1963-09 (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1963-10 (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - October 1963 Central magazine, 1963-10 (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - 10-63-000 to 10-63-079, 1963-10 (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - 10-63-080 to 10-63-142, 1963-10 (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - 10-63-143 to 10-63-203, 1963-10 (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - 10-63-208 to 10-63-257, 1963-10 (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - 10-63-258 to 10-63-305, 1963-10 (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - 10-63-306 to 10-63-380, 1963-10 (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South and North, and Desert, 1963-11 (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - November 1963 Central magazine (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - 11-63-000 to 11-63-078, 1963-11 (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - 11-63-079 to 11-63-147, 1963-11 (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - 11-63-149 to 11-63-206, 1963-11 (Box 138, Folder 6)
  - 11-63-221 to 11-63-286, 1963-11 (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - 11-63-287 to 11-63-345, 1963-11 (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North and Central, 1963-12 (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - December 1963 Central magazine, 1963-12 (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - 12-63-000 to 12-63-066, 1963-12 (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - 12-63-067 to 12-63-134, 1963-12 (Box 139, Folder 6)
  - 12-63-135 to 12-63-182, 1963-12 (Box 139, Folder 7)
  - 12-63-183 to 12-63-220, 1963-12 (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Central, 1964-01 (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - January 1964 magazine (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - 1-64-001 to 1-64-059, 1964-01 (Box 140, Folder 4)
  - 1-64-060 to 1-64-124, 1964-01 (Box 140, Folder 5)
  - 1-64-125 to 1-64-188, 1964-01 (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1964-02 (Box 140, Folder 7)
  - February 1964 magazine (Box 140, Folder 8)
  - 2-64-000 to 2-64-066, 1964-02 (Box 140, Folder 9)
  - 2-64-067 to 2-64-156, 1964-02 (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - 2-64-157 to 2-64-250, 1964-02 (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1964-03 (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - March 1964 Central magazine, 1964-03 (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - 3-64-000 to 3-64-072, 1964-03 (Box 141, Folder 5)
  - 3-64-073 to 3-64-168, 1964-03 (Box 141, Folder 6)
  - 3-64-170 to 3-64-230, 1964-03 (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - 3-64-237 to 3-64-297, 1964-03 (Box 142, Folder 2)
  - 3-64-298 to 3-64-366, 1964-03 (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1964-03 (Box 142, Folder 4)
  - April 1864 Central magazine, 1964-03 (Box 142, Folder 5)
  - 4-64-000 to 4-64-058, 1964-03 (Box 142, Folder 6)
  - 4-64-059 to 4-64-111, 1964-04 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - 4-64-112 to 4-64-168, 1964-04 (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - 4-64-169 to 4-64-252, 1964-04 (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - 4-64-253 to 4-64-344, 1964-04 (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1964-05 (Box 143, Folder 5)
  - May 1964 Central magazine (Box 143, Folder 6)
  - 5-64-000 to 5-64-087, 1964-05 (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - 5-64-089 to 5-64-229, 1964-05 (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - 5-64-166 to 5-64-229, 1964-05 (Box 144, Folder 3)
  - 5-64-232 to 5-64-291, 1964-05 (Box 144, Folder 4)
  - 5-64-292 to 5-64-389, 1964-05 (Box 144, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South, North and Desert, 1964-06 (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - June 1964 Central magazine (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - 6-64-000 to 6-64-076, 1964-06 (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - 6-64-077 to 6-64-155, 1964-06 (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - 6-64-161 to 6-64-241, 1964-06 (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - 6-64-246 to 6-64-329, 1964-06 (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South, North and Desert, 1964-06 (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - July 1964 Central magazine (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - 7-64-000 to 7-64-056, 1964-07 (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - 7-64-057 to 7-64-131, 1964-07 (Box 146, Folder 4)
  - 7-64-132 to 7-64-197, 1964-07 (Box 146, Folder 5)
  - 7-64-198 to 7-64-265, 1964-07 (Box 146, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Central, 1964-08 (Box 146, Folder 7)
  - August 1964 Central magazine (Box 146, Folder 8)
  - 8-64-000 to 8-64-056, 1964-08 (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - 8-64-057 to 8-64-103, 1964-08 (Box 147, Folder 2)
  - 8-64-105 to 8-64-167, 1964-08 (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - 8-64-169 to 8-64-252, 1964-08 (Box 147, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1964-09 (Box 147, Folder 5)
  - September 1964 Central magazine (Box 147, Folder 6)
  - 9-64-000 to 9-64-059, 1964-09 (Box 147, Folder 7)
  - 9-64-060 to 9-64-122, 1964-09 (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - 9-64-123 to 9-64-176, 1964-09 (Box 148, Folder 2)
  - 9-64-177 to 9-64-269, 1964-09 (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1964-10 (Box 148, Folder 4)
  - October 1964 Central magazine (Box 148, Folder 5)
  - 10-64-000 to 10-64-093, 1964-10 (Box 148, Folder 6)
  - 11-64-094 to 11-64-153, 1964-10 (Box 148, Folder 7)
  - 10-64-155 to 10-64-227, 1964-10 (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - 10-64-228 to 10-64-293, 1964-10 (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - 10-64-294 to 10-64-333, 1964-10 (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - 10-64-334 to 10-64-398, 1964-10 (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1964-11 (Box 149, Folder 5)
  - November 1964 Central magazine (Box 149, Folder 6)
  - 11-64-000 to 11-64-065, 1964-11 (Box 149, Folder 7)
  - 11-64-066 to 11-64-131, 1964-11 (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - 11-64-132 to 11-64-184, 1964-11 (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - 11-64-235 to 11-64-234, 1964-11 (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - 11-64-235 to 11-64-331, 1964-11 (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1964-12 (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - December 1964 Central magazine (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - 12-64-000 to 12-64-055, 1964-12 (Box 150, Folder 7)
  - 12-64-056 to 12-64-102, 1964-12 (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - 12-64-103 to 12-64-175, 1964-12 (Box 151, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1965-01 (Box 151, Folder 3)
  - January 1965 Central magazine (Box 151, Folder 4)
  - 1-65-000 to 1-65-062, 1965-01 (Box 151, Folder 5)
  - 1-65-063 to 1-65-132, 1965-01 (Box 151, Folder 6)
  - 1-65-133 to 1-65-222, 1965-01 (Box 151, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1965-02 (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - February 1965 magazine (Box 152, Folder 2)
  - 2-65-065 to 2-65-064, 1965-02 (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - 2-65-065 to 2-65-138, 1965-02 (Box 152, Folder 4)
  - 2-65-139 to 2-65-269, 1965-02 (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1965-02 (Box 152, Folder 6)
  - March 2965 Central magazine, 1965-02 (Box 152, Folder 7)
  - 3-65-000 to 3-65-073, 1965-03 (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - 3-65-074 to 3-65-136, 1965-03 (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - 3-65-138 to 3-65-208, 1965-03 (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - 3-65-209 to 3-65-280, 1965-03 (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - 3-65-283 to 3-65-428, 1965-03 (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1965-04 (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - April 1965 magazine (Box 155, Folder 2)
  - 4-65-001 to 4-65-075, 1965-04 (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - 4-65-076 to 4-65-146, 1965-04 (Box 155, Folder 4)
  - 4-65-148 to 4-65-236, 1965-04 (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - 4-65-237 to 4-65-307, 1965-04 (Box 155, Folder 6)
  - 4-65-308 to 4-65-389, 1965-04 (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1965-05 (Box 156, Folder 2)
  - May 1965 magazine (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - 5-65-000 to 5-65-074, 1965-05 (Box 156, Folder 4)
  - 5-65-075 to 5-65-165, 1965-05 (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - 5-65-166 to 5-65-220, 1965-05 (Box 156, Folder 6)
  - 5-65-221 to 5-65-288, 1965-05 (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - 5-65-291 to 5-65-380, 1965-05 (Box 157, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1965-06 (Box 157, Folder 3)
  - June 1965 Central magazine (Box 157, Folder 4)
  - 6-65-000 to 6-65-089, 1965-06 (Box 157, Folder 5)
  - 6-65-090 to 6-65-169, 1965-06 (Box 157, Folder 6)
  - 6-65-225 to 6-65-291, 1965-06 (Box 158, Folder 1)
  - 6-65-171 to 6-65-224, 1965-06 (Box 158, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1965-07 (Box 158, Folder 3)
  - July 1965 magazine (Box 158, Folder 4)
  - 7-65-001 to 7-65-086, 1965-07 (Box 158, Folder 5)
  - 7-65-087 to 7-65-142, 1965-07 (Box 158, Folder 6)
  - 7-65-143 to 7-65-217, 1965-07 (Box 158, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1965-08 (Box 159, Folder 1)
  - August 1965 magazine (Box 159, Folder 2)
  - 8-65-000 to 8-65-070, 1965-08 (Box 159, Folder 3)
  - 8-65-073 to 8-65-144, 1965-08 (Box 159, Folder 4)
  - 8-65-145 to 8-65-237, 1965-08 (Box 159, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1965-09 (Box 159, Folder 6)
  - September 1965 Central magazine (Box 159, Folder 7)
  - September 1965 "magazine overshoots" (Box 159, Folder 8)
  - 9-65-000 to 9-65-058, 1965-09 (Box 159, Folder 9)
  - 9-65-059 to 9-65-119, 1965-09 (Box 160, Folder 1)
  - 9-65-120 to 9-65-183, 1965-09 (Box 160, Folder 2)
  - 9-65-185 to 9-65-256, 1965-09 (Box 160, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1965-10 (Box 160, Folder 4)
  - October 1965 magazine (Box 160, Folder 5)
  - 10-65-000 to 10-65-088, 1965-10 (Box 160, Folder 6)
  - 10-65-089 to 10-65-136, 1965-10 (Box 161, Folder 1)
  - 10-65-138 to 10-65-202, 1965-10 (Box 161, Folder 2)
  - 10-65-205 to 10-65-261, 1965-10 (Box 161, Folder 3)
  - 10-65-262 to 10-65-373, 1965-10 (Box 161, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1965-11 (Box 161, Folder 5)
  - November 1965 magazine (Box 161, Folder 6)
  - 11-65-000 to 11-65-088, 1965-11 (Box 161, Folder 7)
  - 11-65-089 to 11-65-153, 1965-11 (Box 162, Folder 1)
  - 11-65-154 to 11-65-194, 1965-11 (Box 162, Folder 2)
  - 11-65-195 to 11-65-270, 1965-11 (Box 162, Folder 3)
  - 11-65-271 to 11-65-341, 1965-11 (Box 162, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, and Desert, 1965-12 (Box 162, Folder 5)
  - December 1965 magazine (Box 162, Folder 6)
  - 12-65-000 to 12-65-041, 1965-12 (Box 162, Folder 7)
  - 12-65-042 to 12-65-100, 1965-12 (Box 163, Folder 1)
  - 12-65-101 to 12-65-153, 1965-12 (Box 163, Folder 2)
  - 12-65-154 to 12-65-206, 1965-12 (Box 163, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1966-01 (Box 163, Folder 4)
  - January 1966 magazine (Box 163, Folder 5)
  - 1-66-001 to 1-66-079, 1966-01 (Box 163, Folder 6)
  - 1-66-080 to 1-66-126, 1966-01 (Box 163, Folder 7)
  - 1-66-127 to 1-66-186, 1966-01 (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1966-02 (Box 164, Folder 2)
  - February 1966 Central magazine (Box 164, Folder 3)
  - 2-66-000 to 2-66-074, 1966-02 (Box 164, Folder 4)
  - 2-66-075 to 2-66-149, 1966-02 (Box 164, Folder 5)
  - 2-66-152 to 2-66-266, 1966-02 (Box 164, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1966-03 (Box 164, Folder 7)
  - March 1966 Central magazine (Box 164, Folder 8)
  - 3-66-000 to 3-66-086, 1966-03 (Box 165, Folder 1)
  - 3-66-087 to 3-66-141, 1966-03 (Box 165, Folder 2)
  - 3-66-142 to 3-66-216, 1966-03 (Box 165, Folder 3)
  - 3-66-217 to 3-66-315, 1966-03 (Box 165, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1966-04 (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - April 1966 magazine (Box 165, Folder 6)
  - 4-66-000 to 4-66-080, 1966-04 (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - 4-66-081 to 4-66-155, 1966-04 (Box 166, Folder 2)
  - 4-66-156 to 4-66-243, 1966-04 (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - 4-66-244 to 4-66-302, 1966-04 (Box 166, Folder 4)
  - 4-66-303 to 4-66-355, 1966-04 (Box 166, Folder 5)
  - 4-66-356 to 4-66-418, 1966-04 (Box 166, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1966-05 (Box 167, Folder 1)
  - May 1966 magazine (Box 167, Folder 2)
  - 5-66-001 to 5-66-064, 1966-05 (Box 167, Folder 3)
  - 5-66-066 to 5-66-133, 1966-05 (Box 167, Folder 4)
  - 5-66-134 to 5-66-204, 1966-05 (Box 167, Folder 5)
  - 5-66-205 to 5-66-275, 1966-05 (Box 167, Folder 6)
  - 5-66-276 to 5-66-343, 1966-05 (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - 5-66-344 to 5-66-403, 1966-05 (Box 168, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1966-06 (Box 168, Folder 3)
  - June 1966 magazine (Box 168, Folder 4)
  - 6-66-001 to 6-66-070, 1966-06 (Box 168, Folder 5)
  - 6-66-072 to 6-66-134, 1966-06 (Box 168, Folder 6)
  - 6-66-135 to 6-66-194, 1966-06 (Box 169, Folder 1)
  - 6-66-195 to 6-66-255, 1966-06 (Box 169, Folder 2)
  - 6-66-258 to 6-66-321, 1966-06 (Box 169, Folder 3)
  - 6-66-322 to 6-66-363, 1966-06 (Box 169, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1966-07 (Box 169, Folder 5)
  - July 1966 magazine (Box 169, Folder 6)
  - 7-66-001 to 7-66-057, 1966-07 (Box 169, Folder 7)
  - 7-66-058 to 7-66-125, 1966-07 (Box 170, Folder 1)
  - 7-66-126 to 7-66-176, 1966-07 (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - 7-66-177 to 7-66-225, 1966-07 (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1966-08 (Box 170, Folder 4)
  - August 1966 magazine (Box 170, Folder 5)
  - 8-66-001 to 8-66-057, 1966-08 (Box 170, Folder 6)
  - 8-66-058 to 8-66-124, 1966-08 (Box 170, Folder 7)
  - 8-66-125 to 8-66-172, 1966-08 (Box 171, Folder 1)
  - 8-66-173 to 8-66-231, 1966-08 (Box 171, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1966-09 (Box 171, Folder 3)
  - September 1966 magazine (Box 171, Folder 4)
  - 9-66-001 to 9-66-081, 1966-09 (Box 171, Folder 5)
  - 9-66-082 to 9-66-133, 1966-09 (Box 171, Folder 6)
  - 9-66-135 to 9-66-200, 1966-09 (Box 171, Folder 7)
  - 9-66-201 to 9-66-265, 1966-09 (Box 172, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1966-10 (Box 172, Folder 2)
  - October 1966 magazine (Box 172, Folder 3)
  - 10-66-001 to 10-66-053, 1966-10 (Box 172, Folder 4)
  - 10-66-054 to 10-66-120, 1966-10 (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - 10-66-128 to 10-66-178, 1966-10 (Box 172, Folder 6)
  - 10-66-179 to 10-66-225, 1966-10 (Box 172, Folder 7)
  - 10-66-230 to 10-66-318, 1966-10 (Box 173, Folder 1)
  - 10-66-319 to 10-66-377, 1966-10 (Box 173, Folder 2)
  - 10-66-378 to 10-66-424, 1966-10 (Box 173, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1966-11 (Box 173, Folder 4)
  - November 1966 magazine (Box 173, Folder 5)
  - 11-66-001 to 11-66-053, 1966-11 (Box 173, Folder 6)
  - 11-66-054 to 11-66-102, 1966-11 (Box 173, Folder 7)
  - 11-66-103 to 11-66-150, 1966-11 (Box 174, Folder 1)
  - 11-66-151 to 11-66-224, 1966-11 (Box 174, Folder 2)
  - 11-66-225 to 11-66-297, 1966-11 (Box 174, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1966-12 (Box 174, Folder 4)
  - December 1966 magazine (Box 174, Folder 5)
  - 12-66-001 to 12-66-064, 1966-12 (Box 174, Folder 6)
  - 12-66-065 to 12-66-101, 1966-12 (Box 174, Folder 7)
  - 12-66-102 to 12-66-140, 1966-12 (Box 175, Folder 1)
  - 12-66-141 to 12-66-174, 1966-12 (Box 175, Folder 2)
  - 12-66-176 to 12-66-213, 1966-12 (Box 175, Folder 3)
  - 12-66-214 to 12-66-265, 1966-12 (Box 175, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1967-01 (Box 175, Folder 5)
  - January 1967 Central magazine (Box 175, Folder 6)
  - 1-67-000 to 1-67-058, 1967-01 (Box 175, Folder 7)
  - 1-67-059 to 1-67-101, 1967-01 (Box 175, Folder 8)
  - 1-67-102 to 1-67-152, 1967-01 (Box 176, Folder 1)
  - 1-67-153 to 1-67-201, 1967-01 (Box 176, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1967-02 (Box 176, Folder 3)
  - February 1967 Central magazine (Box 176, Folder 4)
  - 2-67-001 to 2-67-057, 1967-02 (Box 176, Folder 5)
  - 2-67-060 to 2-67-120, 1967-02 (Box 176, Folder 6)
  - 2-67-121 to 2-67-188, 1967-02 (Box 176, Folder 7)
  - 2-67-189 to 2-67-233, 1967-02 (Box 177, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1967-03 (Box 177, Folder 2)
  - March 1967 Central magazine (Box 177, Folder 3)
  - 3-67-000 to 3-67-056, 1967-03 (Box 177, Folder 4)
  - 3-67-057 to 3-67-107, 1967-03 (Box 177, Folder 5)
  - 3-67-110 to 3-67-182, 1967-03 (Box 177, Folder 6)
  - 3-67-183 to 3-67-251, 1967-03 (Box 178, Folder 1)
  - 3-67-252 to 3-67-301, 1967-03 (Box 178, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1967-04 (Box 178, Folder 3)
  - April 1967 Central magazine (Box 178, Folder 4)
  - 4-67-000 to 4-67-064, 1967-04 (Box 178, Folder 5)
  - 4-67-066 to 4-67-132, 1967-04 (Box 178, Folder 6)
  - 4-67-133 to 4-67-215, 1967-04 (Box 179, Folder 1)
  - 4-67-216 to 4-67-318, 1967-04 (Box 179, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1967-05 (Box 179, Folder 3)
  - May 1967 Central magazine (Box 179, Folder 4)
  - 5-67-001 to 5-67-071, 1967-05 (Box 179, Folder 5)
  - 5-67-074 to 5-67-128, 1967-05 (Box 179, Folder 6)
  - 5-67-132 to 5-67-207, 1967-05 (Box 180, Folder 1)
  - 5-67-208 to 5-67-244, 1967-05 (Box 180, Folder 2)
  - 5-67-245 to 5-67-301, 1967-05 (Box 180, Folder 3)
  - 5-67-302 to 5-67-359, 1967-05 (Box 180, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1967-06 (Box 180, Folder 5)
  - June 1967 Central magazine (Box 180, Folder 6)
  - 6-67-001 to 6-67-051, 1967-06 (Box 180, Folder 7)
  - 6-67-052 to 6-67-105, 1967-06 (Box 181, Folder 1)
  - 6-67-106 to 6-67-164, 1967-06 (Box 181, Folder 2)
  - 6-67-167 to 6-67-234, 1967-06 (Box 181, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1967-07 (Box 181, Folder 4)
  - July 1067 Central magazine (Box 181, Folder 5)
  - 7-67-001 to 7-67-073, 1967-07 (Box 181, Folder 6)
  - 7-67-074 to 7-67-135, 1967-07 (Box 181, Folder 7)
  - 7-67-136 to 7-67-200, 1967-07 (Box 182, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1967-08 (Box 182, Folder 2)
  - August 1967 Central magazine (Box 182, Folder 3)
  - 8-67-001 to 8-67-052, 1967-08 (Box 182, Folder 4)
  - 8-67-053 to 8-67-100, 1967-08 (Box 182, Folder 5)
  - 8-67-101 to 8-67-142, 1967-08 (Box 182, Folder 6)
  - 8-67-144 to 8-67-181, 1967-08 (Box 182, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1967-09 (Box 182, Folder 8)
  - September 1967 Central magazine (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - 9-67-001 to 9-67-058, 1967-09 (Box 183, Folder 2)
  - 9-67-061 to 9-67-122, 1967-09 (Box 183, Folder 3)
  - 9-67-123 to 9-67-177, 1967-09 (Box 183, Folder 4)
  - 9-67-178 to 9-67-225, 1967-09 (Box 183, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1967-10 (Box 183, Folder 6)
  - October 1967 Central magazine (Box 183, Folder 7)
  - 10-67-001 to 10-67-061, 1967-10 (Box 184, Folder 1)
  - 10-67-062 to 10-67-115, 1967-10 (Box 184, Folder 2)
  - 10-67-116 to 10-67-163, 1967-10 (Box 184, Folder 3)
  - 10-67-164 to 10-64-212, 1967-10 (Box 184, Folder 4)
  - 10-67-213 to 10-67-269, 1967-10 (Box 184, Folder 5)
  - 10-67-271 to 10-67-321, 1967-10 (Box 184, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1967-11 (Box 185, Folder 1)
  - 11-67-001 to 11-67-068, 1967-11 (Box 185, Folder 2)
  - 11-67-069 to 11-67-132, 1967-11 (Box 185, Folder 3)
  - 11-67-069 to 11-67-132, 1967-11 (Box 185, Folder 4)
  - 11-67-134 to 11-67-193, 1967-11 (Box 185, Folder 5)
  - 11-67-194 to 11-67-257, 1967-11 (Box 185, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1967-11 (Box 185, Folder 7)
  - December 1967 Central magazine (Box 185, Folder 8)
  - 12-67-003 to 12-67-056, 1967-12 (Box 186, Folder 1)
  - 12-67-057 to 12-67-114, 1967-12 (Box 186, Folder 2)
  - 12-67-116 to 12-67-168, 1967-12 (Box 186, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1968-01 (Box 186, Folder 4)
  - January 1968 Central magazine (Box 186, Folder 5)
  - 1-68-000 to 1-68-071, 1968-01 (Box 186, Folder 6)
  - 1-68-074 to 1-68-133, 1968-01 (Box 186, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1968-02 (Box 187, Folder 1)
  - February 1968 Central magazine (Box 187, Folder 2)
  - 2-68-000 to 2-68-056, 1968-02 (Box 187, Folder 3)
  - 2-6-058 to 2-68-123, 1968-02 (Box 187, Folder 4)
  - 2-68-124 to 2-68-181, 1968-02 (Box 187, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1968-03 (Box 187, Folder 6)
  - March 1968 Central magazine, 1968-03 (Box 187, Folder 7)
  - 3-68-001 to 3-68-062, 1968-03 (Box 187, Folder 8)
  - 3-68-063 to 3-68-128, 1968-03 (Box 188, Folder 1)
  - 3-68-129 to 3-68-182, 1968-03 (Box 188, Folder 2)
  - 3-68-183 to 3-68-241, 1968-03 (Box 188, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Central, 1968-04 (Box 188, Folder 4)
  - April 1968 Central magazine (Box 188, Folder 5)
  - 4-68-001 to 4-68-070, 1968-04 (Box 188, Folder 6)
  - 4-68-071 to 4-68-133, 1968-04 (Box 189, Folder 1)
  - 4-68-134 to 4-68-180, 1968-04 (Box 189, Folder 2)